You've been on a bit of a journey with
your song Heavyfoot.
>> Yes.
>> I feel like that song has taken on a lot
of meanings. It feels like it applies to
a lot of different situations.
>> Yeah.
>> What's your relationship to that song
like? Has it changed for you in any way?
>> Yeah, I think it became more of a a
joyful anthem than I had expected. I
think in the beginning, when I was
writing it, you know, I I wanted to
really pinpoint and awaken people to the
things that were happening. But seeing
how it's actually brought joy and
further kind of resilience to those that
are out out front, it's it's it's meant
a lot to see it in that way as well.
Every time we play Heavyfoot, you see
the fans, like they they just the energy
is there, and they all know the words.
It means something to them to say those
words and to have someone also believe
that that's maybe more in the public
eye. It definitely fuels me to keep
making music for them in a in a way that
can inspire.
>> Your approach to what's considered a
protest song.
>> [music]
>> Can you tell me more about like your
relationship to that label?
>> I think it's a beautiful thing. We need
music that stirs and inspires in these
moments. When I go about making my
songs, I'm not necessarily writing them
to [music] be protest songs. Really, I'm
just trying to find and give people a
space to hear the truth or be safe
enough to experience that. [music] If
you want to put a tag to it, that's
fine, too, but I'm more interested in
the inner workings of of the people and
how to just shine a light on things that
maybe a little bit more hard [music] to
to come face to face with.